// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Javascript is an _______ language?",
  answer: "Object-Oriented",
  options: [
    "Object-Oriented",
    "Object-Base",
    "Procedural",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
  answer: "stringify()",
  options: [
    "stringify()",
    "parse()",
    "conver()",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: " Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript",
  answer: "Both A and B",
  options: [
    "Var",
    "let",
    "Both A and B",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: " How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
  answer: "Const",
  options: [
    "Const",
    "Var",
    "Let",
    "Constant"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: " What keyword is used to check whether a given property is valid or not?",
  answer: "in",
  options: [
    "is in",
    "in",
    "exists",
    "lies"
  ]
},
{
numb: 6,
  question: " Which of the following is not a Javascript framework?",
  answer: "cassandra",
  options: [
    "node",
    "vue",
    "react",
    "cassandra"
  ]
},
{
numb: 7,
  question: " How do we write a comment in javascript?",
  answer: "//",
  options: [
    "/*/",
    "//",
    "#",
    "$$"
  ]
},{
numb: 8,
  question: " Which of the following are not server-side Javascript objects",
  answer: "All of the above",
  options: [
    "data",
    "fileupload",
    "function",
    "All of the above"
  ]
},
{
numb: 9,
  question: " What keyword is used to declare an asynchronous function in Javascript?",
  answer: "None of the above",
  options: [
    "async",
    "await",
    "setTimeout",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},
{
numb: 10,
  question: "Upon encountering empty statements, what does the Javascript Interpreter do?",
  answer: "lgnores the statements",
  options: [
    "Throws an error",
    "lgnores the statements",
    "gives a warning",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},


];